yourcareeverywhere.com 2019-03-03

# Privacy Policy | YourCareEverywhere

YourCareEverywhere (“YCE”), a division of MEDHOST Cloud Services, Inc., takes your privacy very seriously. This privacy policy will tell you what information we collect from you and about your use of the site. Except where noted, the Privacy Policy applies to all YCE affiliated web sites, and includes all tools and services offered therein, including the YCE Personal Health Record (“PHR”).  The YCE PHR allows you to collect, manage, and share your health information. If you have registered to access your patient record via a patient portal through your healthcare provider, the Terms of Use and Privacy Policy associated with those records will govern your use and access of any such portal content (even if accessed within the YCE site).

## Information You Give Us

### YCE Registration

By using the functions of the YCE website, you may be asked to provide YCE with data or information about yourself. Any such information retained by YCE will be considered “Personal Information.”  If you choose to register with YCE, you will be asked to enter certain information, such as your name, address, phone number, and email address (“Registration Information”). Such Registration Information will be treated as Personal Information. Some tools and services, including the YCE PHR, permit you to provide information about your health and/or wellness, which is also considered Personal Information.

You will also be asked to select a YCE Community Sponsor, which is a YCE healthcare customer that purchases products and services from YCE. If there is not a YCE Community Sponsor located near you based on the zip code you enter during registration, then the default YCE Community Sponsor will be YCE. If at any time a YCE Community Sponsor becomes available in your area, YCE reserves to right to select them as your YCE Community Sponsor.  Your YCE Community Sponsor may be provided with your registration information, including your name, mailing address, phone number, and email address so that they may contact you. YCE is not responsible for any communications from the YCE Community Sponsor, nor the contents thereof, nor any other activity of the YCE Community Sponsor. You recognize that YCE has no obligation to safeguard or protect any such content or information.

### YCE Public Forums

If you register with YCE, you are provided with the opportunity to participate in community forums and chat rooms, ask questions to experts, and post questions or information about health topics. These communities are public forums and any information that you post or make available should not be considered private.

## Information We Collect During Your Visit

### Cookies, Web Beacons and Similar Technologies

Even if you do not register with YCE, during your use of the web site, we may collect passive information, such as your IP address, through the use of cookies, pixels, beacons, log files, and other technologies such as Google Analytics. This information tells us how you use the web site and allows us to deliver more helpful information, programs, tools, and advertisements. No private data or other personal information [is collected](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245?hl=en) via Google Analytics.  

### Children

The YourCareEverywhere Sites are not intended for use by minors and we do not collect Personal Information from any person we actually know is under the age of 13. A parent or guardian may use the sites on behalf of a minor, and is solely responsible for providing supervision of the minor's use of the sites. The parent or guardian assumes full responsibility for the interpretation and use of any information or suggestions provided.

### How We Use Your Information

As a registered YCE member, you may receive offers for products and services in which you enroll. We DO NOT, however, share your email address or any personal information with third parties (other than your YCE Community Sponsor as set forth above) to provide customer service, to serve content, to serve advertisements, to conduct surveys, to help administer promotional emails, or to administer drawings or contests, but reserve the right to do so in the future with your consent (Opt-in) and subject to applicable laws and regulations. For reasons such as improving personalization of our web site, products, and services, we might receive information about you from third-party sources.

Besides the items listed in the preceding paragraph, we may also use your information to:  

  * Administer your account
  * Register you and give you access to the web site
  * Respond to inquiries you submit to us
  * Fulfill your requests for services, such as newsletters, health trackers, and mobile applications
  * Send you emails, such as newsletters to which you subscribe, and push notifications of news that may be of interest to you
  * Personalize your web site experience
  * Send you promotional information, offers, and other information that may be of interest to you
  * Analyze user data to improve your web site experience

### Aggregation and Statistics

We may use aggregated information to improve the quality of the web site and the services offered, which may include providing statistics to sponsoring hospitals and/or other third parties.

### Information Shared With Third Parties

Except as agreed to by you, or as described in this Privacy Policy, YCE will not disclose any Personal Information about you to third parties, except that we may release information for the purposes of: (a) complying with legal requirements such as a law, regulation, subpoena or court order; or (b) protecting the rights of YCE.

From time-to-time YCE may hire contractors that have access to your Personal Information, to the extent that they access to provide products or services to or on behalf of YCE. All of our contractors are obligated to protect the privacy of your information.

### Third-Party Links

YCE is not responsible for any personal information collected when you click on a third-party link on our website, including advertisements. You should become familiar with the privacy polices of any third-party entity that you visit from the web site. YCE is not responsible for the content or reliability of any websites linked to from its site, and cannot accept liability for any damage or loss arising from reliance on such websites. The links to third party websites are provided for your convenience and information only.

### Updating and Removing Your Information

If you want to correct or update any information previously provided by you, you can log into that specific tool and make changes. If you decide that you do not want your Personal Information used by YCE as described in this Privacy Policy, you should not use or register for any tool that collects such information. If you have registered for YCE and wish to delete any of your Personal Information, please make this request using the Contact Us link below and select Privacy . Upon your request, we will delete your Personal Information from our databases, where feasible. This will not delete or modify any Personal Information previously provided to your YCE Community Sponsor; any modifications to such information must be made through the YCE Community Sponsor.

If you decide that you do not want to receive personalized communications from YCE, you may “Opt-out” of the service by following the unsubscribe instructions included in each promotional email. . Be aware, however, that opting out may disable certain aspects and benefits of having a YCE account, and such withdrawal of consent will only be effective with regard to YCE communications. Any “opt-out” or other modification of your YCE Community Sponsor’s right to contact you must be made through the YCE Community Sponsor and not through YCE.

### Mobile Applications

YCE may make available mobile applications that provide functionality associated with YCE. The download, installation and use may require that you provide, and YCE may collect, certain information which will be governed by this Privacy Policy.

### Security

YCE takes data security seriously, and we use reasonable security measures to protect your Personal Information. Any data transmitted, processed or stored will be encrypted.

Your unique user ID (Screen Name) and password help protect your Personal Information. YCE uses this information to identify you and allow you access to your account, YCE community chat rooms, any Personal Information you have stored in your account, including any wellness data you may be tracking using our online and mobile tools. You are responsible for the storage and protection of your password and for controlling access to your account using your password.

### Contacting YCE

Please send us an email by using the Contact Us link at the bottom of every page of our site if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the Personal Information we maintain about you.

You can also contact the Privacy Office at:

MEDHOST Cloud Services, Inc.

Attn: Privacy Officer

6550 Carothers Parkway Suite 160,

Franklin, TN 37067

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time.  Any changes will be effective at the time posted unless stated otherwise. For material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you directly by email (sent to the email address specified when you register) and/or by means of a notice on this website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to review the Privacy Policy periodically to stay informed about how we are using and protecting your information. Your continued use of the YCE site will be subject to the revised Privacy Policy. Please exit the web site immediately if you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

Updated: _January 30, 2019_
